Charlotte Hetzler

full-stack developer

Professional Profile

Having studied Business Administration, I worked in the area of finance and accounting at KPMG and BMW before I decided to walk new paths and learn to code. With the participation in the Le Wagon bootcamp in Tel Aviv I discovered a new passion for coding and am now happy to follow this path and expand my knowledge.

Experiences

Computer Programming

Le Wagon / May 2019 - Jul 2019

9-week intensive coding bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES2015, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails. Designed, implemented and shipped to production a clone of AirBnB and a Rails prototype of joyage.fun.

- understanding of programming language structures.
- web development in interaction with different coding lanquages.
- teamwork on github.

International Risk Management

BMW Group / Jul 2017 - Jan 2019

Responsible for setting residual values in local markets based on complex statistical models. Analysing possible impacts on residual values resulting from actual political and regulatory discussions.

- interaction between and dependency on multiple departments.
- deep understanding of statistical model set ups for calculating residual values as well as data analyses with SAS and SQL.

Advisory Financial Services

KPMG AG/ Nov 2014 - Mar 2017

Responsible for consulting international financial institutions on how to implement regulatory changes to conform with legal accounting requirements.

- in-depth understanding of complex problems, such as legal and financial analyses and regulatory work.
- direct client interaction, result presentation and meeting conduction leading to improved collaboration and communication skills as well as professional time management.



info@charlottehetzler.com



+49 178 4664985



Hamburg, Germany

Skills

Ruby on Rails.

HTML5.

CSS.

JavaScript.

Bootstrap.

Microsoft Office.

SAS.

SQL.

Languages

German (native).

English (fluent).

Spanish (basic).

Latin (Latinum).

Greek (Greacum).

Education

B.Sc. Business Administration

Ludwig-Maximilians-University Munich, Germany Oct 2013 - Mar 2017

German Abitur

Christianeum, Grammar School Hamburg, Germany Sep 2005 - Jun 2013